== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
SHELDON:
It's bad enough I'm being taken
(Sheldon:)against my will.
(Sheldon:)I don't see why it has to be in
(Sheldon:)some hippie's
mobile sex dungeon.
(Howard:)Well, Sheldon,
there's something about this van
(Howard:)that you're going to find
very interesting.
(Sheldon:)It runs on syphilis?
(Raj:)This van was owned
and driven by your personal
(Raj:)physics hero...
(Raj:)Richard Feynman.
(Sheldon:)No.
Yeah!
(Howard:)A buddy of mine
let me borrow it.
(Leonard:)This was Feynman's van?
(Leonard:)That's so cool.
(Raj:)Yeah, nothing's been changed
since he drove it.
(Howard:)I bet he picked up a lot of cute
grad students in this bad boy.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, and talked about physics
with them!
(gasps)
(Leonard:)So, are you gonna give us
a clue where we're headed?
(Raj:)Uh, okay, let's see...
(Raj:)They've got spicy food
(Raj:)and there's a chance
you'll get diarrhea.
(Leonard:)India.
(Raj:)We can drive there.
(Leonard:)Your house?